{
    "subject": "resource/Hirotoshi_Masui",
    "predicate": "property/throws",
    "object": "Right",
    "human_readable": "Hirotoshi Masui throws Right.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.918425977230072,
            "question": "Does Hirotoshi Masui throw with his left or right hand?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9032224416732788,
            "question": "How does Hirotoshi Masui throw?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8984900116920471,
            "question": "Which direction does Hirotoshi Masui throw?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8896429538726807,
            "question": "In what direction does Hirotoshi Masui typically throw?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8573057055473328,
            "question": "What is Hirotoshi Masui's throwing style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.853060781955719,
            "question": "What hand does Hirotoshi Masui use to throw?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8356256484985352,
            "question": "Hirotoshi Masui's throwing style is described as what?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8149597644805908,
            "question": "What side does Hirotoshi Masui use for throwing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7974614500999451,
            "question": "Is Hirotoshi Masui a right-handed athlete?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6983689665794373,
            "question": "Is Hirotoshi Masui a left-handed or right-handed thrower?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hirotoshi Masui throws Right.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1970_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Hirotoshi Masui a right-handed athlete?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1970_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What side does Hirotoshi Masui use for throwing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1970_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hirotoshi Masui's throwing style is described as what?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1970_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1970_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1970_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1970_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1970_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1970_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1970_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1970_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1970_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1970_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1970_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for your query:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provided contain information about Hirotoshi Masui, and according to them, he is a right-handed pitcher. This supports the triple that \"Hirotoshi Masui throws Right\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Hirotoshi Masui, indicating that he is a right-handed pitcher. This supports the statement that Hirotoshi Masui throws right."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}